# Jason Perreault

jasonperreault.com | eperreault.jason@gmail.com

#### **Profile:**

Highly motivated, hardworking student interested in doing a summer internship at a company that matters. I have prior work experience at multiple companies where I learned a significant amount about creating long lasting code in real situations, and hope to expand this knowledge even further.

### **Work Experience:**

Software Developer – Shapd (May 2013 – November 2013)

Architected and developed a system allowing users to create custom 3D models in the browser for a 3D printing startup company. Converted all models to STL form and hooked up system to 3D printing services, allowing them to be printed. Created parser for SVG files and allowed users to use a library of premade shapes. Extensive use of many different APIs and libraries.

IT Consultant – OIT Help Services (April 2013 – November 2013)

Member of my school's IT division, where I work with clients to diagnose and solve an extremely wide variety of computer related issues.

Software Engineering Intern – Sonos, Inc. (June 2012 – September 2012)

Developed automated tests for desktop controller GUI with Eggplant scripts and integrated them into the automation infrastructure. Learned to effectively and creatively use a poorly documented programming language. Minimal supervision, worked through problems on my own and reported results and progress. Member of the automation scrum team.

#### **Education:**

University of Massachusetts – Amherst (2011 – Present)

Computer Science major, 3.7 GPA, 2015 anticipated year of graduation

## **Skills and Languages:**

Skilled in JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS. Proficient in C, C++ and Python. Experience with Git, Perforce and SVN. Have worked both remotely and in office situations. References available upon request.